Downtown Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1926-1974, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-22; 22 linear ft.; Reels 5488-5545)
  California Print Makers Society (see: Print Makers Society of California)
  California State College at Long Beach, 1965-1966
  California, University of (see: University of California)
  California Western University, 1960
  Calkins, Deborah, undated, 1941, 1951-1952, 1958-1959, 1963, 1965
  Calray Sales and Service, 1964
  Cambridge Management Co., 1967
  Cambridge Press, 1955
  Camden, Maine Antiques Show, 1956
  Camp, Mrs. Frederick, 1955
  Camp Fund Drive, 1941
  Campbell, Mrs. E. P., 1966
  Campbell Ewald Agency, 1956
  Campbell, Hugo, 1938
  Campbell, Martha (Mrs. William A.), 1963
  Campbell, Mrs. N. Stuart, 1934
  Campini, Frank A., 1958-1959
  Campo and Roberts, Inc., 1965
  Canaday, John, 1960-1961, 1963, 1966
  Canajoharie Library and Art Gallery, 1953, 1964
  Candler, Duncan, 1927-1929, 1932-1933
  Candy, William E., 1964, 1966
  Cane, Melville, 1963
  Canepa, Mrs. E., 1957
  Canner, Julius S., 1960
  Cantey, Becky and/or Sam III, undated, 1951-1955, 1957-1962, 1966-1969
  Canton Art Institute, 1966
  Cantor, Dale, 1961
  Cantor, Joseph, 1962, 1964
  Capalbo, Carmen, 1963, 1965, 1967, 1969
  Cape Cod Village, 1956
  Capital University, 1966, 1968-1969
  Capitol Murals Commission, 1963
  Capper Engraving Co., 1956
  Card, Elizabeth Paine, undated, 1957
  Cardullo, Hugo M., 1961, 1963, 1966-1967
  Carlen, Robert, undated, 1941-1946, 1953-1956, 1963-1964, 1967
  Carleton College, 1963, 1969
  Carleton, Peter F., undated, 1963
  Carleton, Mrs. Winslow, 1963
  Carli, Sandra Lee, 1960
  Carlin Lighting Co., 1960
  Carlisle, Mrs. E. G., 1952
  Carlson, Edith, 1966-1967
  Carlson, Florence, 1960
  Henry L. Carlsruh and Co., Inc., 1967
  Carlyle Gallery, 1934
  Carmeli, Louis, 1952
  Carmitchell, Thomas H., 1953
  Carnegie Corporation, 1941
  Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1958
  Carnegie, Hattie, 1942, 1953
  Carnegie Institute Museum of Art, undated, 1933-1935, 1937-1939, 1941, 1945- 1947, 1949-1951, 1953-1958, 1960, 1962-1965, 1967
  Carnegie Study of the Arts of the United States, 1958-1959
  Carney, J. J., 1956-1957
  Carney, Jack and Marian, undated
  Carney, Mel C., 1961, 1966
  Carpenter, Bert, 1960
  Carpenter, Betty C., 1955
  Carpenter, Charles H., undated, 1948
  Carpenter, E. N., 1956, 1958
  Carpenter, Horace, 1936
  Carpenter, James, 1957
  Carr, R. B., 1968
  Carrich, Margaret, 1950
  Carrie, M. et Mme. Louis, 1964
  Carroll, Mark, 1957
  Carson, David, 1954
  Carson, Lundin and Shaw Architects, 1966
  Carte, Mrs. Dale, 1968
  Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, undated, 1962-1963, 1967-1968
  Amon G. Carter Foundation, 1968
  Carter, Howard, Jr., 1966
  Carter, Nancy F., 1964
  Cartier, Inc., 1955-1956
  Carton, Alexis Wallace, undated, 1962
  Carton, Fred, 1953
  Case, Clarence C., 1958-1959
  Case, Margaret W. (Mrs. C. M., Jr.), undated, 1958
  Cash, Robert A., 1961
  Cashwin, Samuel, 1934
  Cassall, John, 1961
  Cassis, Ann, 1961
  Castel, Irving, 1964
  Castleton China, Inc., 1949, 1955, 1958
  Cathey, Ralph, 1964
  Cathlina, Rose, 1960
  Catholic University of America, 1965
  Catholic War Veterans, Inc., 1940
  Catto, Henry E., Jr., 1963
  Cauman, Mrs. Samuel, 1958
  Caumont, G. E., 1940, 1964
  Cavano, Robert R., 1958-1959
  Caylor, George, 1963
  Cayuga Museum of History and Art, 1944
  CBS, 1963
  Cec[ul?], S. John C., 1953
  Cedar Rapids Art Association, 1952, 1958, 1964-1965, 1967
  Celender, Donald D., 1961-1962
  Census Bureau, 1959
  Centenary College, 1935
  Center for Cross-Cultural Communication, 1962-1964 (see also: Robbins, Warren M.)
  Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1967
  Central Bureau for Registered Addresses, 1930
  Central College, 1955-1956
  Central Petroleum Company, 1959
  Centre de Metiers D'Art, 1965
  Centre Manhattan Realty Co., Inc., 1941
  Centro Internazionale di Arte e di Cultura, 1955
  Century Lighting Co., 1946
  Cerf, Bennett A., 1932, 1951
  Chace, Beatrice O., 1967
  Chace, Mr. and/or Mrs. Malcolm C., Jr., 1959-1961, 1966-1968
  Chadbourn, Phil, 1939, 1943
  Chalet Gallery, 1959
  Chamber of Commerce of Honolulu, 1966
  Chambers, Ernest, 1967
  Chamberlain, Betty, 1959, 1965, 1967-1969
  Champeau, Jean Louis, 1958
  Chana Gallery, 1956
  Chandler, Henry, 1933
  Chanin, Abe L., 1953, 1956
  Chanin, Margot, 1965, 1968
  Channel Master Corp., 1954
  [Channing?], 1947
  Chanticleer Press, Inc., 1959, 1969
  Chanute Times, 1951
  George Chapellier Gallery, 1953, 1962-1963
  Chaplin, C. Hal, 1966
  Char, Stanley, 1952
  Charak, Walter, 1958-1959
  Charles, B., 1956
  Charles-Fourth Gallery, 1953-1954
  Charm, undated, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957
  Charm House Furniture Galleries, 1961
  Charnen, Mrs. D., 1963
  Chase, Bessie E., 1956
  Chase, Edward L., 1932
  Chase, Howard, 1942, 1957
  Chase, Mrs. M. A., 1966
  Chase, Mrs. M. G., 1958
  Chase Manhattan Bank, undated, 1956, 1958-1960, 1962-1969
  Chase, Maurice, undated, 1960
  Chase, Meg, 1961
  Chase National Bank, 1942, 1952, 1954, 1955
  Chase, Ronnie, undated
  Chase, Sally (Mrs. Howard), undated, 1960
  Chatham College, 1959, 1965
  Chatham, Mrs. L. A., 1959
  Chattanooga Art Association, 1949
  Chayes, Antonia, undated
  Cheek, Leslie, undated
  Chelsea Clinton News, 1958
  Cheltenham Township Art Centre, 1952-1953
  Cheney, Sheldon, 1958
  Cheney, Thomas S., 1959
  Cherkasky, Martin, 1965-1966
  Cherry, M. J., 1966-1967
  Chestnut Court Book Shops, Inc., 1957
  Chew, Paul, 1958
  Chewing, John B., 1962
  Chicago Art Institute (see: Art Institute of Chicago)
  Chicago, Arts Club of (see: Arts Club of Chicago)
  Chicago Museum of Contemporary Art (see: Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago)
  Chicago Public Library, 1956, 1967
  Chicago Slide Co., 1934
  Chicago, University of (see: University of Chicago)
  Chidsey, G. Alan, 1957, 1961
  Children's Art Program, 1957-1958
  Childs, Charles D., 1950
  Evander Childs High School, 1949
  Childs Gallery, 1960
  Chimney and Furnace Vacuum Cleaning Corp., 1950
  China Aid Council, 1942
  Chinese Community Center, 1962
  Ching, Mr. and/or Mrs. William, 1963
  Chipp, Herschel B. undated
  Choi, Wook Kyung, 1965
  Chomicky, Yar G., 1964
  Chorley, Kenneth, 1942
  Chow, Raymond, undated, 1968
  Christ-Janer, Albert and/or Virginia, undated, 1954, 1956-1957, 1959-1960, 1963, 1965
  "Christ--The King--The Church," 1960
  Christensen, Erwin O., 1964, 1966
  Christian Art, 1966
  Christian Science Monitor, 1954, 1959
  Christiano, Rudy, 1952
  Chrysler Corporation, 1963
  Chrysler, Walter, Jr., 1935
  Chrysomalides, Despina, 1952-1953
  Cikovsky, Hortense and Nicolay, undated
  Cimmino, Christian V., 1958
  Cincinnati Art Academy (see: Art Academy of Cincinnati)
  Cincinnati Art Museum, undated, 1941, 1944, 1948-1951, 1953-1955, 1957-1960, 1962-1964, 1966
  Cincinnati Contemporary Arts Center (see: Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati)
  Cincinnati Modern Art Society, 1944-1945, 1949, 1951, 1953
  Cincinnati Museum Association, 1932
  Cincinnati, University of (see: University of Cincinnati)
  Cinnamon, Gerald E., 1952, 1955-1956
  Ciranna, Alfonson, 1966
  Circle Gallery, 1967, 1968
  Circle Typewriter Co., 1963
  Cirker Hayes Storage Warehouse, 1966, 1968-1969, 1971
  Citro, Jane W., 1952
  City Art Museum of St. Louis, undated, 1934-1935, 1944-1952, 1954-1961, 1963-1969
  City College, New York, 1955-1956
  City College Press, Inc., 1957
  City of Long Beach, 1953
  City of New York, Department of Finance, 1934
  Clark and Gibby, Inc., 1952
  Clark, Charles D., 1964-1965
  Clark, Mr. and Mrs. Hamilton, 1930
  Clark, Mrs. J. III., undated
  Clark, Kemp, 1964
  Clark, Stephen C., undated, 1949, 1953
  Clarke, Jack, undated, 1956
  Clarke, John Lee, Jr., 1956
  Clawson, Rex, 1953
  Clearing House for American Art, 1953
  Clearwater Art Museum, 1943 (see also: Florida Gulf Coast Art Center)
  Cleary, James N., 1941
  Clements, Geoffrey, 1964-1965, 1968
  Cleveland Institute of Art, 1949, 1956
  Cleveland Museum of Art, 1932-1933, 1935, 1945, 1947, 1951, 1954, 1956, 1958, 1960-1965, 1967
  Cleveland Plain-Dealer, 1951, 1955
  Cleveland Press, 1951
  Clifford, 1942
  Clifton Antique Shop, 1953
  Clinton Prison, 1940
  Clivette, Junyta, 1932
  Cloar, Carroll, undated, 1953, 1958, 1963
  Cloar, Ethel, 1967
  Clowns Unlimited, 1961
  Coale, Rita (Mrs. D. Edgar), 1967
  Coate, Judi, 1962
  Coates, Boo and/or Robert, 1949, 1962-1963, 1965
  Cobb, Hubbard H., 1962
  Cobb, Margaret Ayer, 1958
  Cober Gallery, 1960
  Coblentz, Bart, 1968
  Cochran, Gifford A., 1954-1955
  Cocks, Dorothy, 1962
  Coe College, 1954-1959, 1961
  Coe, John J., 1960, 1962
  Coe, Myrtle H., 1956
  Coffin, Edmund, undated, 1964-1965
  Cogar, James L., 1942
  Cogswell, Mrs. Ledyard, 1963
  Cohen, Alfred B., 1960
  Cohen, George Mitchell, 1958-1959
  Cohen, Herbert L., 1956
  Cohen, Hyman, 1933-1934
  J. M. Cohen, Inc., 1960
  Cohen, Jack H., 1968
  Cohen, Jordan, 1962
  Cohen, Maurice U., 1959
  Cohen, Sheldon S., 1967-1968
  Cohen, Wilfred P., 1958
  Cohn, Mrs. Charles N., 1966
  Cohn, Harold, 1932
  Cohn, Lilian (Mrs. David L.), 1964-1965
  Coiner, Charles T., 1939
  Colby College, undated, 1954, 1956-1957, 1959-1966, 1968
  Cole, Allen O., 1968
  Cole, J. Gerald, 1959
  Cole, Richard, 1967, 1968
  Coleman Art Gallery, 1948-1949, 1955, 1957
  Coleman, Edward J., 1957
  Coleman, Grace N., 1932
  Colin, Mr. and/or Mrs. Ralph F., undated, 1952, 1958, 1961, 1968 (see also: Art Dealers Association)
  "Collectors Choice," 1966
  Collectors' Gallery, Inc., 1957, 1964-1965
  Collectors Press, 1968
  Collectors Society, 1956
  College Art Association, 1933
  College Art Journal, 1953, 1959
  College of William and Mary, 1963 (see also: William and Mary College)
  College of Wooster, 1941
  Collins, Enid D., 1934
  Collins, Robert J., 1958
  Collins, William W., 1969-1970
  Colonial Trust Company, 1949
  Colonial Williamsburg, 1945-1946, 1955-1957, 1959
  Colony Furniture Shops, Inc., 1952
  Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, undated, 1953-1955, 1957, 1959, 1963-1964, 1967
  Colorado, University of (see: University of Colorado)
  Colten, 1963
  Colten Photos, undated, 1940, 1946-1947, 1953
  Coltman, Arthur, 1965-1966
  Columbia Museum of Art, 1951-1952, 1955-1957, 1959-1960, 1962-1963, 1965-1968
  Columbia University, 1952, 1956-1957
  Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1933-1935, 1942, 1949-1950, 1952-1953, 1955-1957, 1959-1960, 1962-1965
  Columbus Museum of Arts and Crafts, Inc., 1956, 1961
  Comeau, Harry A., 1934
  Comet-Ray Letter Service, Inc., 1954, 1960-1969
  Commerce Trust Co., 1964-1966
  Commercial Office Supply, 1962-1963, 1965, 1969
  Commissione Americana per gli Scambi Culturale con l'Italia, 1956
  Committee for the Negro in the Arts, 1950
  Committee of Artists' Societies, 1964
  Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1963
  Committee to Save the Cooper Union Museum, 1963-1964
  Community, 1958
  Community Arts Program, 1954
  Community Coordinating Council of North Queens, 1959
  Comolli and Company, 1958, 1959
  F. E. Compton and Company, 1955, 1957
  Compton, Walter, 1968
  Computer Corporation of America, 1967
  Comsky, David, 1963
  Conant, Mrs. G. P., 1959
  Concordia Teachers College, 1967
  Con-Data Systems, Inc., 1964
  Condé-Nast Publications, Inc., 1932, 1943-1945, 1957
  Condon, R. E., 1956
  Condon, Rudolph, 1964
  Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1953
  Congregation Adath Jeshurun, 1964
  Congregation B'nai Israel, 1963
  Congregation B'nai Torah, 1964
  Congregation Emanu-El, 1959-1960
  Congregation Zichron Ephriam, 1955
  Connecticut Historical Society, 1965-1966
  Connecticut Light and Power Co., 1967
  Connecticut, University of (see: University of Connecticut)
  Connor, Howard, 1964
  Connor, Mr., 1966
  Conrad, Earl, 1964
  Conrad, Joan, 1961
  Conrad, Rupert, 1961
  Consolidated Edison Co., 1938, 1941, 1946-1947, 1950, 1953, 1958, 1961
  Contact Answering, Inc. 1964
  Container Corporation of America, 1959, 1962
  Contemporaries Gallery of Sculpture and Graphic Art, undated, 1956-1957, 1967-1968
  Contemporary American Sculptors, Inc., 1948
  Contemporary Art, undated, 1948-1949
  Contemporary Arts Association, 1949-1951
  Contemporary Arts Association of Houston, Inc., 1950, 1952, 1954-1955, 1963-1965
  Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati, 1954, 1956-1957, 1959, 1960-1961, 1963-1965, 1968
  Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston, 1955-1958 (see also: Houston Museum of Contemporary Art)
  Contemporary Arts Society, Indianapolis, 1963
  Contemporary Christian Art Gallery, 1965
  Contemporary Crafts Museum, 1965
  Contemporary Design, Inc., 1947-1948
  Contemporary Interiors, 1967
  Contemporary Paintings, undated, 1955, 1961
  Contemporary Wallpapers, 1958
  Continental Bank and Trust Company of New York, 1945
  Continental Illinois National Bank and Trust Co. of Chicago, 1958, 1965
  Continental Insurance Co., 1967
  Contreras, Belisario R., 1964
  Cook, Christopher, 1964
  Cook, Mrs. George R., 1960
  Cook, Hereward Lester, 1954
  Cook, Howard, 1950
  Cook, John Alfred and/or Margaret, undated, 1957, 1959-1960, 1962-1964
  Cook, Robert H., 1956-1957
  Cook, Mr., 1956
  Cooley, Peter, 1963
  Coolidge, Mountfort, undated
  Coons, Mr. and/or Mrs. Sheldon, 1940, 1955-1956
  Coopchik, Robert, 1956
  Cooper, Mr. and/or Mrs. David Meade, 1962-1964
  Cooper, Gary and/or Georgia B., 1947, 1949, 1951
  Cooper, Mrs. James, 1955
  Cooper, L. E., 1932
  Cooper, Peter Brintnal, 1961
  Cooper, Samuel C., 1945-1946, 1949, 1962
  Cooper Union Museum (see: Committee to Save the Cooper Union Museum)
  Co-operative Women's Civic League, 1945
  Corbett, Harvey Wiley, 1932-1933
  Corcoran Gallery of Art, undated, 1932-1933, 1935, 1944-1945, 1948, 1950-1953, 1956-1970
  CORE (Congress on Racial Equality) Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund, 1965
  Corinthian Gallery, 1964
  Corn Exchange Safe Deposit Co., 1941
  Corn Valley Historical Society, 1941
  Corn, Wanda, 1964
  Cornell College, 1961
  Cornell University, 1954, 1956-1957, 1959-1960, 1962, 1964, 1966-1967
  Corning Museum of Glass, 1966
  Corson, David T., 1956
  Cortor, Eldzier, 1942
  Cosmopolitan, 1958-1959
  Cosmos Travel Bureau, Inc., 1959
  Costello, Mrs. John J., Jr., 1959
  Louis M. Cottin and Company, 1947
  Country Art Gallery, 1960-1961, 1963-1965
  Country Beautiful, 1965
  County Clerk, New York County, 1956
  Courtais, Henri G., 1955
  Covel, Elizabeth W., 1958
  Covici Friede Inc., 1932
  Covington, W., 1945
  Cowan, Charna and/or Spencer M., 1951, 1953-1957, 1960
  Coward, Thomas R., 1951
  Cowdin, Andrea (Mrs. J. Cheever), 1956
  Cowdrey, Bartlett, 1958-1959
  Cowie Galleries, 1949
  Cowlan, Burt, 1965
  Cowles, Fleur, 1948
  Cowles, Mr. and/or Mrs. Gardner, 1954, 1950
  Gardner Cowles Foundation, 1955-1956
  Cowles, John, 1951, 1956-1957, 1961, 1963-1965
  Cowles, Russell, 1954, 1962
  Cowles Syndicate, 1967-1968
  Cox, Arnold, 1960
  Cox, George, 1967
  Cox, John Rogers, 1951
  Coxe, Mary, undated
  Craft Center, 1964
  Craft, Douglas D., 1961
  Cramer, David A., 1966
  Cramer, Florence B., 1957
  Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1944, 1953, 1958-1959, 1966 (see also: Museum of the Cranbrook Academy of Art)
  Crane, Charles L., 1960
  Crane, Harriet, 1956
  Crane, Helen (Mrs. Harry H.), 1961
  Crane Kalman Gallery, 1962
  Crane, Margery A. (Mrs. Ralph T., Jr.), 1959
  Crass, Roger, 1960
  Craven, George N., 1957, 1959
  Craven, Wayne, 1961, 1967-1968
  Crawford, John M., Jr., undated, 1960-1961
  Crawford, Peggy and/or Ralston, 1958, 1963
  Creative Art, 1932
  Creekmore, Raymond, 1934
  Crehan, Hubert, 1955
  Pachita Crespi Gallery, undated
  Crichlow, Ernest, undated
  Crisera, Joseph, 1956
  Crispo, Andrew, 1968
  Crispp, Norman, 1969
  Criss, Francis, 1958
  Crockett, Elizabeth A., 1964
  Cronin, John F., 1965
  Cronin, Richard, 1966
  Caresse Crosby Gallery of Modern Art, 1945
  Cross and Brown Company, 1960, 1962, 1966
  Cross, Harold F., 1965
  Cross, John M., 1969
  Crossgrove, Roger L., 1963
  Crossman, Jerome K., 1956
  Crotty Heating and Cooling Corp., 1941
  Crow, Tramwell, 1967
  Crowell-Collier Educational Corporation, 1966
  Crowell, Merle, 1934
  Crowell, Rodger Palea, undated
  Thomas Y. Crowell Company, 1956
  Crowley, M. J., 1960-1961
  Crown Publishers, Inc., 1965, 1966, 1969
  Crowninshield, Frank, undated, 1930-1934, 1939, 1941, 1945
  Crozier, Mrs. Emmet, 1961
  Crumbach, Mrs. Simeon, 1955
  Crye, Caroll, 1952
  Joan Crystal Gallery, 1963
  Cudahy, Bettina (Mrs. Anthony B.), 1954-1955
  Cuddeback, Charles H., 1944
  Cue, 1962-1963
  Culberg, M.E., 1951-1952
  Cullen, Countee, 1943
  Cullen, William, 1958
  Culler, George, 1962
  Cullman, Mrs. Howard, 1960
  Cummer Gallery of Art, 1965, 1968-1969
  Cummings, Bill, 1965
  Cummings, Marian (Mrs. e. e.), undated, 1959, 1963
  Cummings, Millie and/or Willard H., undated, 1955, 1957-1958, 1960-1965
  Cummings, Minnette (Mrs. H. King), undated
  Cummings, Mr. and/or Mrs. Nathan, 1952-1954, 1956, 1959, 1967-1968
  Cummings, Paul, undated,1968
  Cummins, Ralph H., 1964
  Cunningham, Charles C., undated, 1965-1967
  Curl, Huldah Whipple, 1961
  Curran, Ona (Mrs. Harold P.), 1965
  Current Biography, 1964
  Currier Gallery of Art, undated, 1948-1949, 1954-1957, 1959-1963, 1966
  Currier, Stephen E., 1958
  Curry, Larry, 1968
  Curtis, George A., 1962
  Curtis Lighting, Incorporated, 1945
  Cushing, George M., Jr., undated
  Customs Bureau, 1959, 1962 (see also: U.S. Customs Service)
  Cutler, Carol, 1961
  Cutler, Vergne, 1955
  Cutting, Helen (Mrs. Charles Suydam), undated, 1946-1947, 1949, 1956-1958, 1960-1961
  Cutting, Heyward, 1960, 1962-1965, 1967
  D Contemporary Art Gallery, 1955-1962 (see also: Terry Dintenfass, Inc.)
  Daché, Lilly, 1944
  Dahill, Tom, Sr., 1956, 1958
  Dahlberg, Edward, 1957-1959
  Dailey, George A., 1952
  Dale, Mrs. Chester, 1967
  Dale County War Memorial Library, 1957
  Dallas Morning News, 1956
  Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1958-1963 (see also: Dallas Society for Contemporary Arts)
  Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, undated, 1934-1935, 1940-1942, 1945, 1951-1954, 1957-1959, 1961-1965
  Dallas Society for Contemporary Arts, 1956-1957 (see also: Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts)
  Dallas Theatre Center, 1967
  Dallas, University of (see: University of Dallas)
  Dallas Young Collections, 1956 (see also: Young Collections)
  Dallett, Ione Robinson, 1940
  Dalton, Harry L., 1965, 1966
  Dambrov, Alan S., 1968
  Dame, Laurence, 1958
  D'Amelio, Joseph A., 1964
  Dameshek, William, 1962-1964
  Damico, J., 1958-1959
  Dana, Lester, 1956
  Dana, Mr. and/or Mrs. Richard H., undated, 1958, 1964
  Danbury Scott-Fanton Museum and Historical Society, Inc., 1958
  Dane, Joseph Bert, 1958
  Danhausen, Eldon, 1954
  Daniel, Allen S., 1952
  Daniel, Charles, 1932, 1959
  Daniel, Edwin J., 1950
  Daniell, George, 1956
  Daniels, A. T., 1953
  Danish Information Office, 1959
  Dann, Gertrude H. (Mrs. David S.), undated, 1956, 1960
  Bernard Dannenberg Galleries, 1966, 1968
  Danoff, I. Michael, 1965
  Danzig, Lamont E., 1969
  Danzig, Mrs. Sidney J., 1963
  Darbee, Mrs. William, 1939
  D'Arcy Advertising Company, 1959
  Darmstadt-Eberstadt, 1963
  Darrah, Frank J., 1944
  Darriau, Jean, 1956
  Darrow, Paul, 1955-1956
  Dart, Gawaine, 1960
  Dartiel, 1969
  d'Artista, Robert, 1952
  Dartmouth College, 1930, 1935, 1944, 1948, 1951-1952, 1962-1963
  Dartmouth College Club, 1959
  Dartt, James G., 1949
  Elsie Das Hawaiian Originals, 1962
  Daughters of the American Revolution Museum, 1941
  Davenport, Bill, 1964
  Davenport Municipal Art Gallery, 1951-1952, 1958-1959, 1963, 1968
  Davenport, Roselle, 1963
  David, David, 1931, 1961
  David Gallery, undated, 1966
  David's Sholom, 1965
  Davidson, undated
  Davidson, Mrs. Daniel, 1955
  Davidson, Leroy B., 1947
  Davidson, W. F., 1939
  Davis, Allan A., 1964
  Davis and Heffner, 1951
  Davis, Bernard, 1940
  Davis, Bette, 1941
  Davis, Dorland and Co., 1942
  Davis, Mrs. Dwight F., 1938
  Davis, Mrs. Edwin L., 1965
  Davis, Emma Lou, undated, 1942
  Davis, Ferdinand H., 1961
  Davis, Floyd, 1938
  Davis Galleries, undated
  Davis, Ginger, 1968
  Davis, Henry A., 1956
  Davis, Hubert, 1941
  Davis, Janet Evans, 1959
  Davis, Kathe, 1959
  Davis, Lew, 1959
  Davis, Mary M. (Mrs. Keith), 1962
  Davis, Richard, 1931
  Davis, Richard B., 1966
  Davis, Richard S., 1951-1954
  Davis, Robert Tyler, 1943, 1959
  Davis, Roselle and/or Stuart, 1931, 1946, 1953-1956, 1959, 1963-1965, 1967
  Davis, Virginia Stetiley, undated
  Davis, Mrs. Walter, 1963
  Davison Art Center, 1952-1953, 1955 (see also: Wesleyan University)
  Davisson, 1940
  Dawson, Sam, 1959
  Day and Meyer, Murray and Young Corp., 1968
  Day and Zimmerman, Inc., 1955
  Day, Lucy D. (Mrs. W. E., Jr.), undated, 1962
  Days, Jacquelyn, 1968
  Dayton Art Institute, 1934, 1939, 1949, 1951, 1953, 1955, 1958-1959, 1966-1967
  Dayton Typographic Service, 1965
  Dayton's Gallery, 1966
  Deal, Ogden, 1960
  Dealers of American Art, 1957 (see also: New York Dealers of American Art)
  "Dealers Show American Art," 1941
  Dearden, Francis Greenwood, 1952-1953
  de Bedts, Ralph F. and/or Ruth, 1958, 1961
  Decca Records, Inc., 1943
  de Coninck, Suzanne, 1960
  Decorators Club, Inc., 1939, 1941, 1943
  De Cordova and Dana Museum and Park, undated, 1951, 1957-1958, 1959, 1961, 1963
  de Cordova, Nancy, 1964
  Major William F. Deegan Post No. 1, 1941
  Defenbacher, Dan S., 1958, 1966
  de Gampes, Enriqueta, 1953
  de Golier, Mary Ann (Mrs. Ralph J.), undated, 1947, 1964, 1966-1967
  de Graaf, Mrs. Peter, 1967
  de Graaff, Mr. and/or Mrs. Jan, 1948, 1951-1952
  Jack De Gregory and Company, 1967
  de Groot, Adelade Milton, undated, 1941
  De Haan, Norman R., 1965-1966
  de Hauke, Cesar M., 1958-1959
  DeHaven, Heidi, 1959
  De Hovitz, Bernard, 1958-1959, 1961
  Deitsch, Peter H., 1959
  Deitsch Gallery, 1956
  de Koven, Daniel, undated, 1950, 1956, 1959-1960
  Delahantey, William E., 1954
  deLara, Jea'Belle, 1957
  Delavan, Elizabeth G. and/or Nelson B., Jr., 1963, 1965-1966
  Delaware Art Center, 1959-1960, 1967 (see also: Society of the Fine Arts)
  Delaware, University of (see: University of Delaware)
  Delaware Valley Art Foundation, 1959
  K. Delbanco, Incorporated, 1957
  Delfino, Peter, undated, 1962
  Isaac Delgado Museum of Art, 1949, 1959-1960
  Delhorn, M. M., 1969
  de Liagre, Alfred, 1959
  Delloye, Charles, 1962
  Delmonico's Hotel, 1964
  Delphic Studios, 1933
  Delta Letter Service, undated
  Demarest Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1956-1957
  de Menil, Mr. and Mrs., 1965
  de Menil, Mr. and/or Mrs. Jean, 1951, 1955
  de Menil, John, 1957, 1962
  Demeter, Mary, 1958
  De Mille, Agnes George, 1966
  Demmer, Vera Haberle, 1962
  Demmer, Victor, 1967
  Demotte, L. J., 1933
  Eva De Nagy Gallery, 1960
  Dendal, Yves, 1957
  Denenberg, Stuart R., 1966
  De Niro, Helen M., 1952
  Denman, Carl, 1963-1965
  Denman, Jean and/or John C., undated, 1946-1949, 1951, 1953-1956, 1958-1960, 1962, 1964, 1966
  Dennison, Carl L., undated, 1965-1968
  J. M. Dent and Sons Ltd., 1959
  Denver Art Museum, 1935, 1937-1939, 1942, 1951, 1955-1960, 1963, 1965-1966, 1968
  Department of Commerce and Public Events, New York City, 1957
  Department of Labor, 1952
  Department of State, 1946, 1951, 1960-1963, 1965-1971 (see also: U.S. Department of State)
  Department of the Army, Reorientation Branch, 1949-1950 (see also: U. S. Army)
  De Pauw University, 1959
  Deramus, Mrs. John, 1961
  Derecktor, Lina P., 1956
  Derkert, Carlo, 1963
  Derrickson, Howard, 1949
  Derskey, Morris, 1955
  Derum, Ardis V., 1958
  de Santamaria, Marta, 1955
  De Schepper, Gerald R., 1964
  De Sharp, Ernest, undated, 1942, 1944
  J. Blaise de Sibour and Company, 1953, 1956-1957
  Design, 1948, 1951
  Design Associates Gallery International, 1967
  Design Publishing Co., 1947
  Deskey, Donald, 1932